[
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "हिंदी में \"किताब\" का अर्थ क्या है?",
        "options": [
            "Book",
            "Pen",
            "Table",
            "Chair"
        ],
        "answer": "Book",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 1
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "\"नमस्ते\" का उपयोग किस स्थिति में होता है?",
        "options": [
            "पूजा",
            "स्नान",
            "स्वागत",
            "समर्थन"
        ],
        "answer": "स्वागत",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 1
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "How do you say \"good morning\" in Hindi?",
        "options": [
            "नमस्ते (Namaste)",
            "गुड मॉर्निंग (Good Morning)",
            "सुबह बख़ैर (Subah Bakhair)",
            "वाह क्या बात है! (Wah Kya Baat Hai!)"
        ],
        "answer": "सुबह बख़ैर (Subah Bakhair)",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 1
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "What is the Hindi word for \"hello\"?",
        "options": [
            "पूजा",
            "स्नान",
            "धन्यवाद (Dhanyavad)",
            "नमस्ते (Namaste)"
        ],
        "answer": "नमस्ते (Namaste)",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 1
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "How do you say \"thank you\" in Hindi to someone older than you?",
        "options": [
            "शुक्रिया (Shukriya)",
            "धन्यवाद (Dhanyavad)",
            "आपका बहुत-बहुत धन्यवाद (Aapka bahut-bahut dhanyavad)",
            "जी धन्यवाद (Ji dhanyavad)"
        ],
        "answer": "आपका बहुत-बहुत धन्यवाद (Aapka bahut-bahut dhanyavad)",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 1
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "Can you identify the correct Hindi numeral for the number 3?",
        "options": [
            "१",
            "२",
            "३",
            "४"
        ],
        "answer": "३",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 2
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "Which Hindi sentence means \"My name is John\"?",
        "options": [
            "मेरा नाम जॉन है। (Mera naam John hai.)",
            "जॉन मेरा नाम है। (John mera naam hai.)",
            "है जॉन मेरा नाम। (Hai John mera naam.)",
            "जॉन है मेरा नाम। (John hai mera naam.)"
        ],
        "answer": "मेरा नाम जॉन है। (Mera naam John hai.)",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 2
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for \"telephone\"?",
        "options": [
            "टेलीफोन (Telephone)",
            "छाता (Chhata)",
            "साइकिल (Cycle)",
            "पानी (Paani)"
        ],
        "answer": "टेलीफोन (Telephone)",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 2
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "हिंदी में \"शिक्षक\" का अर्थ क्या है?",
        "options": [
            "Doctor",
            "Teacher",
            "Engineer",
            "Farmer"
        ],
        "answer": "Teacher",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 3
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for \"credit card\"?",
        "options": [
            "पुस्तक (Pustak)",
            "लिफाफा (Lifafa)",
            "क्रेडिट कार्ड (Credit Card)",
            "समाचार-पत्र (Samachar-patra)"
        ],
        "answer": "क्रेडिट कार्ड (Credit Card)",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 2
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for \"Please\"?",
        "options": [
            "बाएं (Baayein)",
            "नमस्कार (Namaskaar)",
            "कृपया करके (Kripaya Karke)",
            "क्षमा कीजिए (Kshama Kijiye)"
        ],
        "answer": "कृपया करके (Kripaya Karke)",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 2
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "How do you ask \"How are you?\" in Hindi in a formal way?",
        "options": [
            "आप कैसे हैं? (Aap kaise hain?)",
            "तुम कैसे हो? (Tum kaise ho?)",
            "क्या हाल है? (Kyahaal hai?)",
            "नमस्ते! (Namaste!)"
        ],
        "answer": "आप कैसे हैं? (Aap kaise hain?)",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 3
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "Conjugate the Hindi verb \"जाना\" (jaana, meaning \"to go\") in the future tense for \"we\".",
        "options": [
            "जाएंगे (jayenge)",
            "जा रहे हैं (ja rahe hain)",
            "गए हैं (gaye hain)",
            "जाओ (jao)"
        ],
        "answer": "जाएंगे (jayenge)",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 3
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "Which of these words is NOT a synonym for \"happy\" in Hindi?",
        "options": [
            "खुश (Khush)",
            "हर्षित (Harshith)",
            "प्रसन्न (Prasann)",
            "दुखी (Dukhi)"
        ],
        "answer": "दुखी (Dukhi)",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 3
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "Which of these words is NOT a synonym for \"beautiful\" in Hindi?",
        "options": [
            "सुंदर (Sundar)",
            "सुन्दर (Sundar)",
            "खूबसूरत (Khoobsurat)",
            "प्यारा (Pyaara)"
        ],
        "answer": "प्यारा (Pyaara)",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 4
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for \"Thank you very much\"?",
        "options": [
            "मुझे नहीं पता। (Mujhe nahi pata.)",
            "क्षमा कीजिए। (Kshama kijiye.)",
            "बहुत-बहुत धन्यवाद। (Bahut-bahut dhanyavaad.)",
            "वाह-वाह! (Wah-Wah!)"
        ],
        "answer": "बहुत-बहुत धन्यवाद। (Bahut-bahut dhanyavaad.)",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 4
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "Which Hindi word describes something that is \"दर्दनाक\" (dardnak, meaning \"painful\")?",
        "options": [
            "सुंदर (Sundar)",
            "सुखदायक (Sukhadaayak)",
            "सुगंधित (Sugandhit)",
            "भयानक (Bhayanak)"
        ],
        "answer": "भयानक (Bhayanak)",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 4
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "\"मैं भूखा हूँ\" का अर्थ क्या है?",
        "options": [
            "I am thirsty",
            "I am hungry",
            "I am tired",
            "I am happy"
        ],
        "answer": "I am hungry",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 5
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "Select the antonym for \"जलता हुआ\":",
        "options": [
            "Glowing",
            "Burning",
            "Extinguished",
            "Shining"
        ],
        "answer": "Extinguished",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 3
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "Form the correct sentence: \"वह बहुत अच्छा गाता है.\"",
        "options": [
            "He sings very well",
            "He dances very well",
            "He speaks very well",
            "He paints very well"
        ],
        "answer": "He sings very well",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 4
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "Can you identify the correct instrumental case of the Hindi noun \"लड़का\" (ladka, meaning \"boy\")?",
        "options": [
            "लड़के से (ladke se)",
            "लड़के में (ladke mein)",
            "लड़के द्वारा (ladke dvara)",
            "लड़के को (ladke ko)"
        ],
        "answer": "लड़के से (ladke se)",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 4
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "Identify the correct possessive construction for \"My sister's book\" in Hindi.",
        "options": [
            "बहन की किताब (bahan ki kitaab)",
            "किताब की बहन (kitaab ki bahan)",
            "मेरी किताब की बहन (meri kitaab ki bahan)",
            "बहन मेरी किताब (bahan meri kitaab)"
        ],
        "answer": "बहन की किताब (bahan ki kitaab)",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 5
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "Which famous Hindi poem starts with the line \"वंदे मातरम्, सुजला सुफलाम्...\" (Vande Mataram, Sujla Suphalam...)?",
        "options": [
            "राष्ट्रगीत (Rashtrageet) (National Anthem)",
            "सारे जहां से अच्छा हिन्दोस्तान हमारा (Sare Jahan Se Achcha Hindustan Hamara)",
            "मेघदूत (Meghadoota)",
            "नुश्रवां का बगीचा (Nushrat ka Baghicha)"
        ],
        "answer": "राष्ट्रगीत (Rashtrageet) (National Anthem)",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 5
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "What Hindi idiom does \"हाथी के दाँत खाने के बहाने, दर्शन कराना\" (haathi ke daant khaane ke bahane, darshan karana) mean?",
        "options": [
            "To kill two birds with one stone",
            "To use a pretext for a personal gain",
            "To look before you leap",
            "To cry over spilled milk"
        ],
        "answer": "To use a pretext for a personal gain",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 5
    },
    {
        "language": "Hindi",
        "question": "Translate \"आत्मविश्वास\" into English",
        "options": [
            "Self-confidence",
            "Self-control",
            "Self-esteem",
            "Self-discipline"
        ],
        "answer": "Self-confidence",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 5
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "Translate the word \"मित्र\" into English.",
        "options": [
            "Friend",
            "Enemy",
            "Love",
            "Family"
        ],
        "answer": "Friend",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 1
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "How do you say \"good morning\" in Hindi?",
        "options": [
            "नमस्ते (Namaste)",
            "गुड मॉर्निंग (Good Morning)",
            "सुबह बख़ैर (Subah Bakhair)",
            "वाह क्या बात है! (Wah Kya Baat Hai!)"
        ],
        "answer": "सुबह बख़ैर (Subah Bakhair)",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 1
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "Translate the word \"खुशी\" into English.",
        "options": [
            "Happiness",
            "Sadness",
            "Anger",
            "Fear"
        ],
        "answer": "Happiness",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 1
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "Complete the sentence: \"I ____ to the store.\"",
        "options": [
            "am going",
            "will go",
            "goes",
            "gone"
        ],
        "answer": "am going",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 1
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "Which English word means \"विद्यार्थी\" (vidyarthi) in Hindi?",
        "options": [
            "Teacher",
            "Student",
            "Doctor",
            "Engineer"
        ],
        "answer": "Student",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 1
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "Translate the phrase \"मेरा नाम जॉन है।\" into English.",
        "options": [
            "My name is John.",
            "I am John.",
            "John is my name.",
            "John, my name."
        ],
        "answer": "My name is John.",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 2
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for \"Please\"?",
        "options": [
            "बाएं (Baayein)",
            "नमस्कार (Namaskaar)",
            "कृपया करके (Kripaya Karke)",
            "क्षमा कीजिए (Kshama Kijiye)"
        ],
        "answer": "कृपया करके (Kripaya Karke)",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 2
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "Translate the word \"बहुत\" into English.",
        "options": [
            "A lot",
            "Little",
            "Big",
            "Small"
        ],
        "answer": "A lot",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 2
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "Identify the correct instrumental case of the Hindi noun \"गीत\" (geet, meaning \"song\")?",
        "options": [
            "गीत से (geet se)",
            "गीत में (geet mein)",
            "गीत द्वारा (geet dvara)",
            "गीत को (geet ko)"
        ],
        "answer": "गीत से (geet se)",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 3
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "How do you ask \"How are you?\" in Hindi in a formal way?",
        "options": [
            "आप कैसे हैं? (Aap kaise hain?)",
            "तुम कैसे हो? (Tum kaise ho?)",
            "क्या हाल है? (Kyahaal hai?)",
            "नमस्ते! (Namaste!)"
        ],
        "answer": "आप कैसे हैं? (Aap kaise hain?)",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 2
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for \"Thank you very much\"?",
        "options": [
            "मुझे नहीं पता। (Mujhe nahi pata.)",
            "क्षमा कीजिए। (Kshama kijiye.)",
            "बहुत-बहुत धन्यवाद। (Bahut-bahut dhanyavaad.)",
            "वाह-वाह! (Wah-Wah!)"
        ],
        "answer": "बहुत-बहुत धन्यवाद। (Bahut-bahut dhanyavaad.)",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 2
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "Translate the word \"दिन\" into English.",
        "options": [
            "Day",
            "Night",
            "Sun",
            "Moon"
        ],
        "answer": "Day",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 3
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "Translate the phrase \"मुझे थोड़ा समय दो\" into English.",
        "options": [
            "Give me some time.",
            "Take some time.",
            "Have some time.",
            "Waste some time."
        ],
        "answer": "Give me some time.",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 3
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for \"दिनचर्या\"?",
        "options": [
            "Daily routine",
            "Weekly schedule",
            "Monthly plan",
            "Yearly calendar"
        ],
        "answer": "Daily routine",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 3
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "Translate the phrase \"आपका स्वागत है\" into English.",
        "options": [
            "You're welcome.",
            "Thank you.",
            "Hello.",
            "Goodbye."
        ],
        "answer": "You're welcome.",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 4
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "Identify the correct plural form of the word \"child\".",
        "options": [
            "Children",
            "Childs",
            "Childers",
            "Childs"
        ],
        "answer": "Children",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 4
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "Translate the word \"उत्साही\" into English.",
        "options": [
            "Excited",
            "Calm",
            "Sad",
            "Angry"
        ],
        "answer": "Excited",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 4
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "Complete the sentence: \"She ____ to the market.\"",
        "options": [
            "go",
            "goes",
            "going",
            "gone"
        ],
        "answer": "goes",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 5
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "Translate the phrase \"मैं तुमसे प्यार करता हूँ।\" into English.",
        "options": [
            "I love you.",
            "You love me.",
            "We love together.",
            "Love is with you."
        ],
        "answer": "I love you.",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 3
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for \"महान\"?",
        "options": [
            "Great",
            "Small",
            "Beautiful",
            "Sad"
        ],
        "answer": "Great",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 4
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "Translate the phrase \"बहुत कम\" into English.",
        "options": [
            "Very less",
            "Very much",
            "Very little",
            "Very large"
        ],
        "answer": "Very little",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 4
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "Identify the correct plural form of the word \"mouse\".",
        "options": [
            "Mouses",
            "Mice",
            "Mousen",
            "Mouse"
        ],
        "answer": "Mice",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 5
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "Translate the phrase \"बहुत अच्छा\" into English.",
        "options": [
            "Very good",
            "Very bad",
            "Very sad",
            "Very happy"
        ],
        "answer": "Very good",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 5
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "What is the antonym for the English word \"beautiful\"?",
        "options": [
            "Ugly",
            "Pretty",
            "Attractive",
            "Lovely"
        ],
        "answer": "Ugly",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 5
    },
    {
        "language": "English",
        "question": "Translate the word \"बहन\" into English.",
        "options": [
            "Sister",
            "Brother",
            "Mother",
            "Father"
        ],
        "answer": "Sister",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 5
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "Translate the word \"amigo\" into Spanish.",
        "options": [
            "Friend",
            "Enemy",
            "Love",
            "Family"
        ],
        "answer": "Friend",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 1
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "How do you say \"good morning\" in Spanish?",
        "options": [
            "Hola",
            "Buenas noches",
            "Buenos días",
            "Adiós"
        ],
        "answer": "Buenos días",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 1
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "Translate the word \"familia\" into Spanish.",
        "options": [
            "Happiness",
            "Sadness",
            "Family",
            "Fear"
        ],
        "answer": "Family",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 1
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "Complete the sentence: \"Yo ____ en casa.\"",
        "options": [
            "soy",
            "seré",
            "estoy",
            "estaré"
        ],
        "answer": "estoy",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 1
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "Which Spanish word means \"estudiante\" in English?",
        "options": [
            "Teacher",
            "Student",
            "Doctor",
            "Engineer"
        ],
        "answer": "Student",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 1
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for \"telephone\"?",
        "options": [
            "el teléfono",
            "el agua",
            "un paraguas",
            "una bicicleta"
        ],
        "answer": "el teléfono",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 2
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "How do you say \"Good afternoon\"?",
        "options": [
            "Adios",
            "Buenas tardes",
            "Buenos días",
            "Buenas noches"
        ],
        "answer": "Buenas tardes",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 2
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "How do you say \"Good evening\"?",
        "options": [
            "Muchas gracias",
            "unas llaves",
            "Buenas noches",
            "Adios"
        ],
        "answer": "Buenas noches",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 2
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for \"Please\"?",
        "options": [
            "Por favor",
            "izquierda",
            "Perdón",
            "Hola"
        ],
        "answer": "Por favor",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 3
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "Translate the phrase \"Mi nombre es Juan.\" into Spanish.",
        "options": [
            "My name is Juan",
            "I am Juan",
            "Juan is my name",
            "Juan, my name"
        ],
        "answer": "My name is Juan",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 2
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for \"Por favor\"?",
        "options": [
            "Hello",
            "Thank you",
            "Excuse me",
            "Please"
        ],
        "answer": "Please",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 2
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "How do you ask \"How are you?\" in Spanish in a formal way?",
        "options": [
            "¿Cómo estás?",
            "¿Cómo te llamas?",
            "¿Cómo está usted?",
            "¿Qué tal?"
        ],
        "answer": "¿Cómo está usted?",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 3
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for \"Gracias\"?",
        "options": [
            "Hello",
            "Thank you",
            "Excuse me",
            "Please"
        ],
        "answer": "Thank you",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 3
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "Translate the word \"libro\" into Spanish.",
        "options": [
            "Book",
            "Table",
            "Chair",
            "Pen"
        ],
        "answer": "Book",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 3
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "What does the acronym \"UNESCO\" stand for?",
        "options": [
            "United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization",
            "Universal Network of Educators and Scholars Organization",
            "Union of Nations for Educational and Scientific Cooperation",
            "United Nations for Education, Science, and Cultural Organization"
        ],
        "answer": "United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 4
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "Translate the phrase \"No hay problema\" into English.",
        "options": [
            "No problem",
            "Big problem",
            "Some problem",
            "Many problems"
        ],
        "answer": "No problem",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 4
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for \"feliz\"?",
        "options": [
            "Sad",
            "Happy",
            "Angry",
            "Excited"
        ],
        "answer": "Happy",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 4
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "Complete the sentence: \"Ella ____ al cine.\"",
        "options": [
            "ir",
            "va",
            "voy",
            "vamos"
        ],
        "answer": "va",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 5
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "Translate the phrase \"Muy bien\" into English.",
        "options": [
            "Very good",
            "Very bad",
            "Very sad",
            "Very happy"
        ],
        "answer": "Very good",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 3
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "Translate the word \"computadora\" into Spanish.",
        "options": [
            "Computer",
            "Television",
            "Radio",
            "Telephone"
        ],
        "answer": "Computer",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 4
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "Identify the correct plural form of the word \"niño\".",
        "options": [
            "Niños",
            "Niñoes",
            "Niñós",
            "Niñis"
        ],
        "answer": "Niños",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 4
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "Translate the phrase \"Tu corazón es muy grande.\" into Spanish.",
        "options": [
            "Your heart is very big",
            "My heart is very big",
            "His heart is very big",
            "Her heart is very big"
        ],
        "answer": "Your heart is very big",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 5
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for \"excelente\"?",
        "options": [
            "Great",
            "Small",
            "Beautiful",
            "Sad"
        ],
        "answer": "Great",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 5
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "Translate the phrase \"Te amo.\" into Spanish.",
        "options": [
            "I love you",
            "You love me",
            "We love together",
            "Love is with you"
        ],
        "answer": "I love you",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 5
    },
    {
        "language": "Spanish",
        "question": "Identify the correct instrumental case of the Spanish noun \"canción\" (song).",
        "options": [
            "Canción por",
            "Canción en",
            "Canción con",
            "Canción a"
        ],
        "answer": "Canción con",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 5
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "Translate the word \"amico\" into Italian.",
        "options": [
            "Friend",
            "Enemy",
            "Love",
            "Family"
        ],
        "answer": "Friend",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 1
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "How do you say \"good morning\" in Italian?",
        "options": [
            "Ciao",
            "Buonasera",
            "Buongiorno",
            "Arrivederci"
        ],
        "answer": "Buongiorno",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 1
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "Translate the word \"famiglia\" into Italian.",
        "options": [
            "Happiness",
            "Sadness",
            "Family",
            "Fear"
        ],
        "answer": "Family",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 1
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "Complete the sentence: \"Io ____ a casa.\"",
        "options": [
            "sono",
            "sarò",
            "sto",
            "starò"
        ],
        "answer": "sto",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 1
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "Which Italian word means \"studente\" in English?",
        "options": [
            "Teacher",
            "Student",
            "Doctor",
            "Engineer"
        ],
        "answer": "Student",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 1
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "Translate the word \"casa\" into Italian.",
        "options": [
            "House",
            "Car",
            "Tree",
            "School"
        ],
        "answer": "House",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 2
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "What is the Italian word for \"hello\"?",
        "options": [
            "Ciao",
            "Arrivederci",
            "Buonasera",
            "Grazie"
        ],
        "answer": "Ciao",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 2
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "Translate the word \"sole\" into Italian.",
        "options": [
            "Moon",
            "Sun",
            "Star",
            "Cloud"
        ],
        "answer": "Sun",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 2
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for \"buona notte\"?",
        "options": [
            "Good morning",
            "Good night",
            "Good afternoon",
            "Goodbye"
        ],
        "answer": "Good night",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "difficultyLevel": 1,
        "point": 1,
        "excerciseNumber": 3
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "Translate the phrase \"Mi chiamo Marco.\" into Italian.",
        "options": [
            "My name is Marco",
            "I am Marco",
            "Marco is my name",
            "Marco, my name"
        ],
        "answer": "My name is Marco",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 2
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for \"Per favore\"?",
        "options": [
            "Hello",
            "Thank you",
            "Excuse me",
            "Please"
        ],
        "answer": "Please",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 2
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "How do you ask \"How are you?\" in Italian in a formal way?",
        "options": [
            "Come stai?",
            "Come ti chiami?",
            "Come sta lei?",
            "Che ne dici?"
        ],
        "answer": "Come sta lei?",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 3
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for \"Grazie\"?",
        "options": [
            "Hello",
            "Thank you",
            "Excuse me",
            "Please"
        ],
        "answer": "Thank you",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 3
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "Translate the word \"libro\" into Italian.",
        "options": [
            "Book",
            "Table",
            "Chair",
            "Pen"
        ],
        "answer": "Book",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 3
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "Translate the phrase \"Non c'è problema\" into English.",
        "options": [
            "No problem",
            "Big problem",
            "Some problem",
            "Many problems"
        ],
        "answer": "No problem",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 4
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for \"felice\"?",
        "options": [
            "Sad",
            "Happy",
            "Angry",
            "Excited"
        ],
        "answer": "Happy",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 4
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "Complete the sentence: \"Lei ____ al cinema.\"",
        "options": [
            "andare",
            "va",
            "vado",
            "andiamo"
        ],
        "answer": "va",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 4
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "Complete the sentence: \"Io ____ italiano.\"",
        "options": [
            "am",
            "is",
            "are",
            "speak"
        ],
        "answer": "speak",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "difficultyLevel": 2,
        "point": 3,
        "excerciseNumber": 5
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "What is the correct translation for \"eccellente\"?",
        "options": [
            "Great",
            "Small",
            "Beautiful",
            "Sad"
        ],
        "answer": "Great",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 3
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "Translate the phrase \"Ti amo.\" into Italian.",
        "options": [
            "I love you",
            "You love me",
            "We love together",
            "Love is with you"
        ],
        "answer": "I love you",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 4
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "Identify the correct instrumental case of the Italian noun \"canzone\" (song).",
        "options": [
            "Canzone per",
            "Canzone in",
            "Canzone con",
            "Canzone a"
        ],
        "answer": "Canzone con",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 4
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "Translate the word \"molto\" into Italian.",
        "options": [
            "Very little",
            "Very much",
            "Very good",
            "Very bad"
        ],
        "answer": "Very much",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 5
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "What is the synonym for the Italian word \"energetico\"?",
        "options": [
            "Dull",
            "Energetic",
            "Calm",
            "Tired"
        ],
        "answer": "Energetic",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 5
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "Translate the phrase \"Il tuo cuore è molto grande.\" into Italian.",
        "options": [
            "Your heart is very big.",
            "My heart is very big.",
            "His heart is very big.",
            "Her heart is very big."
        ],
        "answer": "Your heart is very big.",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 5
    },
    {
        "language": "Italian",
        "question": "Translate the word \"computer\" into Italian.",
        "options": [
            "Computer",
            "Television",
            "Radio",
            "Telephone"
        ],
        "answer": "Computer",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "difficultyLevel":3,
        "point": 5,
        "excerciseNumber": 5
    }
]
